Berat Ucar

Front-End Developer



- ✓ dev.beratucar@gmail.com
 - +905537457033
 - Ankara/Turkey

in Berat Ucar 🕝 Berat Ucar

ON Berat Ucar

Education

Civil Engineering, Gazi University 09/2017 – 10/2022 Ankara, Turkey

Languages

English (B2)

Turkish (Native)

Profile

Junior Front-End Developer with experience in the software development lifecycle (SDLC) in developing and designing user experiences of Internet/Intranet applications using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SASS, React.js, Redux.js MeetingW3C standards. Excellent analytical and logical programming skills with a good understanding at the conceptual level.

Professional Experience

Front-End Developer, Gaming Pro Market ☑

02/2023 - present | United States

- Worked as part of the team on projects; receive regular guidance.
- Worked closely with team members to create consistent, reusable, and maintainable code; designed new software systems or updates to existing systems.
- Coordinated and participated in implementation, testing, and support.
- Responsible for understanding how their work fits into the project objectives.
- Ensured each build functions correctly on mobile, tablet, and desktop devices.

Front-End Developer, Let's Rental Car ☑

01/2023 - 02/2023 | United States

- Followed agile & scrum methods for the development of the product.
- Involving in building multiple UI components from design stage to production stage.
- Performed validation of completed sites including the debugging and testing of code.
- Designed a responsive website using Bootstrap grid system to layout contents that fit different devices including mobile, tablet and desktop.
- Cross-browser tested sites in Microsoft Edge, Safari, Firefox, Chrome and mobile browsers.

Skills

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SASS, React.js, Redux.js, Postman API, REST APIs, Communication, Teamwork, Problem-Solving, Time Management, Organizational, Adaptability

Other (Webpack, Unit Testing, NPM, SDLC, Jira, Scrum, Agile Methods)

Projects

SPA Project 🛮

Single Page Application Project https://github.com/beratucardy/spa-project You can visit my github for more projects and apps like this